

   Computername: SRV1


Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Active Directory Certificate Services
Description  : Active Directory Certificate Services (AD CS) is 
               used to create certification authorities and 
               related role services that allow you to issue and 
               manage certificates used in a variety of 
               applications.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Certification Authority
Description  : Certification Authority (CA) is used to issue and 
               manage certificates. Multiple CAs can be linked 
               to form a public key infrastructure.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Certificate Enrollment Policy Web Service
Description  : The Certificate Enrollment Policy Web Service 
               enables users and computers to obtain certificate 
               enrollment policy information even when the 
               computer is not a member of a domain or if a 
               domain-joined computer is temporarily outside the 
               security boundary of the corporate network. The 
               Certificate Enrollment Policy Web Service works 
               with the Certificate Enrollment Web Service to 
               provide policy-based automatic certificate 
               enrollment for these users and computers.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Certificate Enrollment Web Service
Description  : The Certificate Enrollment Web Service enables 
               users and computers to enroll for and renew 
               certificates even when the computer is not a 
               member of a domain or if a domain-joined computer 
               is temporarily outside the security boundary of 
               the computer network. The Certificate Enrollment 
               Web Service works together with the Certificate 
               Enrollment Policy Web Service to provide 
               policy-based automatic certificate enrollment for 
               these users and computers.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Certification Authority Web Enrollment
Description  : Certification Authority Web Enrollment provides a 
               simple Web interface that allows users to perform 
               tasks such as request and renew certificates, 
               retrieve certificate revocation lists (CRLs), and 
               enroll for smart card certificates.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Network Device Enrollment Service
Description  : Network Device Enrollment Service makes it 
               possible to issue and manage certificates for 
               routers and other network devices that do not 
               have network accounts.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Online Responder
Description  : Online Responder makes certificate revocation 
               checking data accessible to clients in complex 
               network environments.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Active Directory Domain Services
Description  : Active Directory Domain Services (AD DS) stores 
               information about objects on the network and 
               makes this information available to users and 
               network administrators. AD DS uses domain 
               controllers to give network users access to 
               permitted resources anywhere on the network 
               through a single logon process.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Active Directory Federation Services
Description  : Active Directory Federation Services (AD FS) 
               provides simplified, secured identity federation 
               and Web single sign-on (SSO) capabilities. AD FS 
               includes a Federation Service that enables 
               browser-based Web SSO.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Active Directory Lightweight Directory Services
Description  : Active Directory Lightweight Directory Services 
               (AD LDS) provides a store for 
               application-specific data, for directory-enabled 
               applications that do not require the 
               infrastructure of Active Directory Domain 
               Services. Multiple instances of AD LDS can exist 
               on a single server, each of which can have its 
               own schema.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Active Directory Rights Management Services
Description  : Active Directory Rights Management Services (AD 
               RMS) helps you protect information from 
               unauthorized use. AD RMS establishes the identity 
               of users and provides authorized users with 
               licenses for protected information.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Active Directory Rights Management Server
Description  : Active Directory Rights Management Services (AD 
               RMS) helps you protect information from 
               unauthorized use. AD RMS establishes the identity 
               of users and provides authorized users with 
               licenses for protected information.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Identity Federation Support
Description  : Identity Federation Support leverages federated 
               trust relationships between your organization and 
               other organizations to establish user identities 
               and provide access to protected information 
               created by either organization. For example, a 
               trust created with Active Directory Federation 
               Services can be used to establish user identities 
               for AD RMS.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Device Health Attestation
Description  : Device Health Attestation
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : DHCP Server
Description  : Dynamic Host Configuration Protocol (DHCP) Server 
               enables you to centrally configure, manage, and 
               provide temporary IP addresses and related 
               information for client computers.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : DNS Server
Description  : Domain Name System (DNS) Server provides name 
               resolution for TCP/IP networks. DNS Server is 
               easier to manage when it is installed on the same 
               server as Active Directory Domain Services. If 
               you select the Active Directory Domain Services 
               role, you can install and configure DNS Server 
               and Active Directory Domain Services to work 
               together.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : File and Storage Services
Description  : File and Storage Services includes services that 
               are always installed, as well as functionality 
               that you can install to help manage file servers 
               and storage.
Installed    : True
InstallState : Installed

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : File and iSCSI Services
Description  : File and iSCSI Services provides technologies 
               that help you manage file servers and storage, 
               reduce disk space utilization, replicate and 
               cache files to branch offices, move or fail over 
               a file share to another cluster node, and share 
               files by using the NFS protocol.
Installed    : True
InstallState : Installed

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : File Server
Description  : File Server manages shared folders and enables 
               users to access files on this computer from the 
               network.
Installed    : True
InstallState : Installed

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : BranchCache for Network Files
Description  : BranchCache for Network Files provides support 
               for BranchCache on this file server. BranchCache 
               is a wide area network (WAN) bandwidth 
               optimization technology that caches content from 
               your main office content servers at branch office 
               locations, allowing client computers at branch 
               offices to access the content locally rather than 
               over the WAN. After you complete installation, 
               you must share folders and enable hash generation 
               for shared folders by using Group Policy or Local 
               Computer Policy.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Data Deduplication
Description  : Data Deduplication saves disk space by storing a 
               single copy of identical data on the volume.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : DFS Namespaces
Description  : DFS Namespaces enables you to group shared 
               folders located on different servers into one or 
               more logically structured namespaces. Each 
               namespace appears to users as a single shared 
               folder with a series of subfolders. However, the 
               underlying structure of the namespace can consist 
               of numerous shared folders located on different 
               servers and in multiple sites.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : DFS Replication
Description  : DFS Replication is a multimaster replication 
               engine that enables you to synchronize folders on 
               multiple servers across local or wide area 
               network (WAN) network connections. It uses the 
               Remote Differential Compression (RDC) protocol to 
               update only the portions of files that have 
               changed since the last replication. DFS 
               Replication can be used in conjunction with DFS 
               Namespaces, or by itself.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : File Server Resource Manager
Description  : File Server Resource Manager helps you manage and 
               understand the files and folders on a file server 
               by scheduling file management tasks and storage 
               reports, classifying files and folders, 
               configuring folder quotas, and defining file 
               screening policies.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : File Server VSS Agent Service
Description  : File Server VSS Agent Service enables you to 
               perform volume shadow copies of applications that 
               store data files on this file server.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : iSCSI Target Server
Description  : iSCSI Target Server provides services and 
               management tools for iSCSI targets.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : iSCSI Target Storage Provider (VDS and VSS 
               hardware providers)
Description  : iSCSI Target Storage Provider enables 
               applications on a server that are connected to an 
               iSCSI target to perform volume shadow copies of 
               data on iSCSI virtual disks. It also enables you 
               to manage iSCSI virtual disks by using older 
               applications that require a Virtual Disk Service 
               (VDS) hardware provider, such as the Diskraid 
               command.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Server for NFS
Description  : Server for NFS enables this computer to share 
               files with UNIX-based computers and other 
               computers that use the network file system (NFS) 
               protocol.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Work Folders
Description  : Work Folders provides a way to use work files 
               from a variety of computers, including work and 
               personal devices. You can use Work Folders to 
               host user files and keep them synchronized - 
               whether users access their files from inside the 
               network or from across the Internet.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Storage Services
Description  : Storage Services provides storage management 
               functionality that is always installed and cannot 
               be removed.
Installed    : True
InstallState : Installed

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Host Guardian Service
Description  : The Host Guardian Service (HGS) server role 
               provides the Attestation & Key Protection 
               services that enable Guarded Hosts to run 
               Shielded virtual machines. The Attestation 
               service validates Guarded Host identity & 
               configuration. The Key Protection service enables 
               distributed access to encrypted transport keys to 
               enable Guarded Hosts to unlock and run Shielded 
               virtual machines.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Hyper-V
Description  : Hyper-V provides the services that you can use to 
               create and manage virtual machines and their 
               resources. Each virtual machine is a virtualized 
               computer system that operates in an isolated 
               execution environment. This allows you to run 
               multiple operating systems simultaneously.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Print and Document Services
Description  : Print and Document Services enables you to 
               centralize print server and network printer 
               management tasks. With this role, you can also 
               receive scanned documents from network scanners 
               and route the documents to a shared network 
               resource, Windows SharePoint Services site, or 
               e-mail addresses.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Print Server
Description  : Print Server includes the Print Management 
               snap-in, which is used for managing multiple 
               printers or print servers and migrating printers 
               to and from other Windows print servers.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : LPD Service
Description  : Line Printer Daemon (LPD) Service enables 
               UNIX-based computers or other computers using the 
               Line Printer Remote (LPR) service to print to 
               shared printers on this server.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Remote Access
Description  : Remote Access provides seamless connectivity 
               through DirectAccess, VPN, and Web Application 
               Proxy. DirectAccess provides an Always On and 
               Always Managed experience. RAS provides 
               traditional VPN services, including site-to-site 
               (branch-office or cloud-based) connectivity. Web 
               Application Proxy enables the publishing of 
               selected HTTP- and HTTPS-based applications from 
               your corporate network to client devices outside 
               of the corporate network. Routing provides 
               traditional routing capabilities, including NAT 
               and other connectivity options. RAS and Routing 
               can be deployed in single-tenant or multi-tenant 
               mode.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : DirectAccess and VPN (RAS)
Description  : DirectAccess gives users the experience of being 
               seamlessly connected to their corporate network 
               any time they have Internet access. With 
               DirectAccess, mobile computers can be managed any 
               time the computer has Internet connectivity, 
               ensuring mobile users stay up-to-date with 
               security and system health policies. VPN uses the 
               connectivity of the Internet plus a combination 
               of tunnelling and data encryption technologies to 
               connect remote clients and remote offices.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Routing
Description  : Routing provides support for NAT Routers, LAN 
               Routers running BGP, RIP, and multicast capable 
               routers (IGMP Proxy).
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Web Application Proxy
Description  : Web Application Proxy enables the publishing of 
               selected HTTP- and HTTPS-based applications from 
               your corporate network to client devices outside 
               of the corporate network. It can use AD FS to 
               ensure that users are authenticated before they 
               gain access to published applications. Web 
               Application Proxy also provides proxy 
               functionality for your AD FS servers.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Remote Desktop Services
Description  : Remote Desktop Services enables users to access 
               virtual desktops, session-based desktops, and 
               RemoteApp programs. Use the Remote Desktop 
               Services installation to configure a Virtual 
               machine-based or a Session-based desktop 
               deployment.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Remote Desktop Connection Broker
Description  : Remote Desktop Connection Broker (RD Connection 
               Broker) allows users to reconnect to their 
               existing virtual desktops, RemoteApp programs, 
               and session-based desktops. It enables even load 
               distribution across RD Session Host servers in a 
               session collection or across pooled virtual 
               desktops in a pooled virtual desktop collection, 
               and provides access to virtual desktops in a 
               virtual desktop collection.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Remote Desktop Licensing
Description  : Remote Desktop Licensing (RD Licensing) manages 
               the licenses required to connect to a Remote 
               Desktop Session Host server or a virtual desktop. 
               You can use RD Licensing to install, issue, and 
               track the availability of licenses.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Remote Desktop Virtualization Host
Description  : Remote Desktop Virtualization Host (RD 
               Virtualization Host) enables users to connect to 
               virtual desktops by using RemoteApp and Desktop 
               Connection.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Volume Activation Services
Description  : Volume Activation Services enables you to 
               automate and simplify the management of Key 
               Management Service (KMS) host keys and the volume 
               key activation infrastructure for a network. With 
               this service you can install and manage a KMS 
               host, or configure Microsoft Active 
               Directory-Based Activation to provide volume 
               activation for domain-joined systems.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Web Server (IIS)
Description  : Web Server (IIS) provides a reliable, manageable, 
               and scalable Web application infrastructure.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Web Server
Description  : Web Server provides support for HTML Web sites 
               and optional support for ASP.NET, ASP, and Web 
               server extensions. You can use the Web Server to 
               host an internal or external Web site or to 
               provide an environment for developers to create 
               Web-based applications.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Common HTTP Features
Description  : Common HTTP Features supports basic HTTP 
               functionality, such as delivering standard file 
               formats and configuring custom server properties. 
               Use Common HTTP Features to create custom error 
               messages, to configure how the server responds to 
               requests that do not specify a document, or to 
               automatically redirect some requests to a 
               different location.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Default Document
Description  : Default Document lets you configure a default 
               file for the Web server to return when users do 
               not specify a file in a request URL. Default 
               documents make it easier and more convenient for 
               users to reach your Web site.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Directory Browsing
Description  : Directory Browsing lets users to see the contents 
               of a directory on your Web server. Use Directory 
               Browsing to enable an automatically generated 
               list of all directories and files available in a 
               directory when users do not specify a file in a 
               request URL and default documents are either 
               disabled or not configured.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : HTTP Errors
Description  : HTTP Errors allows you to customize the error 
               messages returned to users' browsers when the Web 
               server detects a fault condition. Use HTTP errors 
               to provide users with a better user experience 
               when they run up against an error message. 
               Consider providing users with an e-mail address 
               for staff who can help them resolve the error.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Static Content
Description  : Static Content allows the Web server to publish 
               static Web file formats, such as HTML pages and 
               image files. Use Static Content to publish files 
               on your Web server that users can then view using 
               a Web browser.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : HTTP Redirection
Description  : HTTP Redirection provides support to redirect 
               user requests to a specific destination. Use HTTP 
               redirection whenever you want customers who might 
               use one URL to actually end up at another URL. 
               This is helpful in many situations, from simply 
               renaming your Web site, to overcoming a domain 
               name that is difficult to spell, or forcing 
               clients to use a secure channel.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : WebDAV Publishing
Description  : WebDAV Publishing (Web Distributed Authoring and 
               Versioning) enables you to publish files to and 
               from a Web server by using the HTTP protocol. 
               Because WebDAV uses HTTP, it works through most 
               firewalls without modification.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Health and Diagnostics
Description  : Health and Diagnostics provides infrastructure to 
               monitor, manage, and troubleshoot the health of 
               Web servers, sites, and applications.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : HTTP Logging
Description  : HTTP Logging provides logging of Web site 
               activity for this server. When a loggable event, 
               usually an HTTP transaction, occurs, IIS calls 
               the selected logging module, which then writes to 
               one of the logs stored in the file system of the 
               Web server. These logs are in addition to those 
               provided by the operating system.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Custom Logging
Description  : Custom Logging provides support for logging Web 
               server activity in a format that differs 
               considerably from the manner in which IIS 
               generates log files. Use custom to create your 
               own logging module. Custom logging modules are 
               added to IIS by registering a new COM component 
               that implements ILogPlugin or ILogPluginEx.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Logging Tools
Description  : Logging Tools provides infrastructure to manage 
               Web server logs and automate common logging tasks.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : ODBC Logging
Description  : ODBC Logging provides infrastructure that 
               supports logging Web server activity to an 
               ODBC-compliant database. With a logging database, 
               you can programmatically display and manipulate 
               data from the logging database on an HTML page. 
               You might do this to search logs for specific 
               events to call out user defined events that you 
               want to monitor.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Request Monitor
Description  : Request Monitor provides infrastructure to 
               monitor Web application health by capturing 
               information about HTTP requests in an IIS worker 
               process. Administrators and developers can use 
               Request Monitor to understand which HTTP requests 
               are executing in a worker process when the worker 
               process has become unresponsive or very slow.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Tracing
Description  : Tracing provides infrastructure to diagnose and 
               troubleshoot Web applications. With failed 
               request tracing, you can troubleshoot difficult 
               to capture events like poor performance, or 
               authentication related failures. This feature 
               buffers trace events for a request and only 
               flushes them to disk if the request falls into a 
               user-configured error condition.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Performance
Description  : Performance provides infrastructure for output 
               caching by integrating the dynamic output-caching 
               capabilities of ASP.NET with the static 
               output-caching capabilities that were present in 
               IIS 6.0. IIS also lets you use bandwidth more 
               effectively and efficiently by using common 
               compression mechanisms such as Gzip and Deflate.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Static Content Compression
Description  : Static Content Compression provides 
               infrastructure to configure HTTP compression of 
               static content. This allows more efficient use of 
               bandwidth. Unlike dynamic responses, compressed 
               static responses can be cached without degrading 
               CPU resources.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Dynamic Content Compression
Description  : Dynamic Content Compression provides 
               infrastructure to configure HTTP compression of 
               dynamic content. Enabling dynamic compression 
               always gives you more efficient utilization of 
               bandwidth, but if your server's processor 
               utilization is already very high, the CPU load 
               imposed by dynamic compression might make your 
               site perform more slowly.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Security
Description  : Security provides infrastructure for securing the 
               Web server from users and requests. IIS supports 
               multiple authentication methods. Pick an 
               appropriate authentication scheme based upon the 
               role of the server. Filter all incoming requests, 
               rejecting without processing requests that match 
               user defined values, or restrict requests based 
               on originating address space.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Request Filtering
Description  : Request Filtering screens all incoming requests 
               to the server and filters these requests based on 
               rules set by the administrator. Many malicious 
               attacks share common characteristics, like 
               extremely long requests, or requests for an 
               unusual action. By filtering requests, you can 
               attempt to mitigate the impact of these type 
               attacks.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Basic Authentication
Description  : Basic authentication offers strong browser 
               compatibility. Appropriate for small internal 
               networks, this authentication method is rarely 
               used on the public Internet. Its major 
               disadvantage is that it transmits passwords 
               across the network using an easily decrypted 
               algorithm. If intercepted, these passwords are 
               simple to decipher. Use SSL with Basic 
               authentication.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Centralized SSL Certificate Support
Description  : Centralized SSL Certificate Support enables you 
               to manage SSL server certificates centrally using 
               a file share. Maintaining SSL server certificates 
               on a file share simplifies management since there 
               is one place to manage them.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Client Certificate Mapping Authentication
Description  : Client Certificate Mapping Authentication uses 
               client certificates to authenticate users. A 
               client certificate is a digital ID from a trusted 
               source. IIS offers two types of authentication 
               using client certificate mapping. This type uses 
               Active Directory to offer one-to-one certificate 
               mappings across multiple Web servers.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Digest Authentication
Description  : Digest authentication works by sending a password 
               hash to a Windows domain controller to 
               authenticate users. When you need improved 
               security over Basic authentication, consider 
               using Digest authentication, especially if users 
               who must be authenticated access your Web site 
               from behind firewalls and proxy servers.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : IIS Client Certificate Mapping Authentication
Description  : IIS Client Certificate Mapping Authentication 
               uses client certificates to authenticate users. A 
               client certificate is a digital ID from a trusted 
               source. IIS offers two types of authentication 
               using client certificate mapping. This type uses 
               IIS to offer one-to-one or many-to-one 
               certificate mapping. Native IIS mapping of 
               certificates offers better performance.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : IP and Domain Restrictions
Description  : IP and Domain Restrictions allow you to enable or 
               deny content based upon the originating IP 
               address or domain name of the request. Instead of 
               using groups, roles, or NTFS file system 
               permissions to control access to content, you can 
               specific IP addresses or domain names.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : URL Authorization
Description  : URL Authorization allows you to create rules that 
               restrict access to Web content. You can bind 
               these rules to users, groups, or HTTP header 
               verbs. By configuring URL authorization rules, 
               you can prevent employees who are not members of 
               certain groups from accessing content or 
               interacting with Web pages.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Windows Authentication
Description  : Windows authentication is a low cost 
               authentication solution for internal Web sites. 
               This authentication scheme allows administrators 
               in a Windows domain to take advantage of the 
               domain infrastructure for authenticating users. 
               Do not use Windows authentication if users who 
               must be authenticated access your Web site from 
               behind firewalls and proxy servers.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Application Development
Description  : Application Development provides infrastructure 
               for developing and hosting Web applications. Use 
               these features to create Web content or extend 
               the functionality of IIS. These technologies 
               typically provide a way to perform dynamic 
               operations that result in the creation of HTML 
               output, which IIS then sends to fulfill client 
               requests.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : .NET Extensibility 3.5
Description  : .NET extensibility allows managed code developers 
               to change, add and extend web server 
               functionality in the entire request pipeline, the 
               configuration, and the UI. Developers can use the 
               familiar ASP.NET extensibility model and rich 
               .NET APIs to build Web server features that are 
               just as powerful as those written using the 
               native C++ APIs.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : .NET Extensibility 4.6
Description  : .NET extensibility allows managed code developers 
               to change, add and extend web server 
               functionality in the entire request pipeline, the 
               configuration, and the UI. Developers can use the 
               familiar ASP.NET extensibility model and rich 
               .NET APIs to build Web server features that are 
               just as powerful as those written using the 
               native C++ APIs.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Application Initialization
Description  : Application Initialization perform expensive web 
               application initialization tasks before serving 
               web pages.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : ASP
Description  : Active Server Pages (ASP) provides a server side 
               scripting environment for building Web sites and 
               Web applications. Offering improved performance 
               over CGI scripts, ASP provides IIS with native 
               support for both VBScript and JScript. Use ASP if 
               you have existing applications that require ASP 
               support. For new development, consider using 
               ASP.NET.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : ASP.NET 3.5
Description  : ASP.NET provides a server side object oriented 
               programming environment for building Web sites 
               and Web applications using managed code. ASP.NET 
               is not simply a new version of ASP. Having been 
               entirely re-architected to provide a highly 
               productive programming experience based on the 
               .NET Framework, ASP.NET provides a robust 
               infrastructure for building web applications.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : ASP.NET 4.6
Description  : ASP.NET provides a server side object oriented 
               programming environment for building Web sites 
               and Web applications using managed code. ASP.NET 
               4.6 is not simply a new version of ASP. Having 
               been entirely re-architected to provide a highly 
               productive programming experience based on the 
               .NET Framework, ASP.NET provides a robust 
               infrastructure for building web applications.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : CGI
Description  : CGI defines how a Web server passes information 
               to an external program. Typical uses might 
               include using a Web form to collect information 
               and then passing that information to a CGI script 
               to be emailed somewhere else. Because CGI is a 
               standard, CGI scripts can be written using a 
               variety of programming languages. The downside to 
               using CGI is the performance overhead.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : ISAPI Extensions
Description  : Internet Server Application Programming Interface 
               (ISAPI) Extensions provides support for dynamic 
               Web content developing using ISAPI extensions. An 
               ISAPI extension runs when requested just like any 
               other static HTML file or dynamic ASP file. Since 
               ISAPI applications are compiled code, they are 
               processed much faster than ASP files or files 
               that call COM+ components.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : ISAPI Filters
Description  : Internet Server Application Programming Interface 
               (ISAPI) Filters provides support for Web 
               applications that use ISAPI filters. ISAPI 
               filters are files that can extend or change the 
               functionality provided by IIS. An ISAPI filter 
               reviews every request made to the Web server, 
               until the filter finds one that it needs to 
               process.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Server Side Includes
Description  : Server Side Includes (SSI) is a scripting 
               language used to dynamically generate HTML pages. 
               The script runs on the server before the page is 
               delivered to the client and typically involves 
               inserting one file into another. You might create 
               an HTML navigation menu and use SSI to 
               dynamically add it to all pages on a Web site.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : WebSocket Protocol
Description  : IIS 10.0 and ASP.NET 4.6 support writing server 
               applications that communicate over the WebSocket 
               Protocol.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : FTP Server
Description  : FTP Server enables the transfer of files between 
               a client and server by using the FTP protocol. 
               Users can establish an FTP connection and 
               transfer files by using an FTP client or 
               FTP-enabled Web browser.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : FTP Service
Description  : FTP Service enables FTP publishing on a Web 
               server.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : FTP Extensibility
Description  : FTP Extensibility enables support for FTP 
               extensibility features such as custom providers, 
               ASP.NET users or IIS Manager users.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Management Tools
Description  : Management Tools provide infrastructure to manage 
               a Web server that runs IIS 10. You can use the 
               IIS user interface, command-line tools, and 
               scripts to manage the Web server. You can also 
               edit the configuration files directly.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : IIS 6 Management Compatibility
Description  : IIS 6 Management Compatibility provides forward 
               compatibility for your applications and scripts 
               that use the two IIS APIs, Admin Base Object 
               (ABO) and Active Directory Service Interface 
               (ADSI). You can use existing IIS 6 scripts to 
               manage the IIS 10 Web server.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : IIS 6 Metabase Compatibility
Description  : IIS 6 Metabase Compatibility provides 
               infrastructure to query and configure the 
               metabase so that you can run applications and 
               scripts migrated from earlier versions of IIS 
               that use Admin Base Object (ABO) or Active 
               Directory Service Interface (ADSI) APIs.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : IIS 6 Scripting Tools
Description  : IIS 6 Scripting Tools provide the ability to 
               continue using IIS 6 scripting tools that you 
               built to manage IIS 6 in IIS 10, especially if 
               your applications and scripts that use ActiveX 
               Data Objects (ADO) or Active Directory Service 
               Interface (ADSI) APIs. IIS 6 Scripting Tools 
               require Windows Process Activation Service 
               Configuration API.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : IIS 6 WMI Compatibility
Description  : IIS 6 WMI Compatibility provides Windows 
               Management Instrumentation (WMI) scripting 
               interfaces to programmatically manage and 
               automate tasks for IIS 10.0 Web server, from a 
               set of scripts that you created in the WMI 
               provider. This service includes the WMI CIM 
               Studio, WMI Event Registration, WMI Event Viewer, 
               and WMI Object Browser tools to manage sites.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : IIS Management Scripts and Tools
Description  : IIS Management Scripts and Tools provide 
               infrastructure to programmatically manage an IIS 
               10 Web server by using commands in a command 
               window or by running scripts. You can use these 
               tools when you want to automate commands in batch 
               files or when you do not want to incur the 
               overhead of managing IIS by using the user 
               interface.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Management Service
Description  : Management Service allows the Web server to be 
               managed remotely from another computer using IIS 
               Manager.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Windows Server Essentials Experience
Description  : Windows Server Essentials Experience sets up the 
               IT infrastructure and provides powerful functions 
               such as PC backups that helps protect data, and 
               Remote Web Access that helps access business 
               information from virtually anywhere. Windows 
               Server Essentials also helps you to easily and 
               quickly connect to cloud-based applications and 
               services to extend the functionality of your 
               server.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Windows Server Update Services
Description  : Windows Server Update Services allows network 
               administrators to specify the Microsoft updates 
               that should be installed, create separate groups 
               of computers for different sets of updates, and 
               get reports on the compliance levels of the 
               computers and the updates that must be installed.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : WID Connectivity
Description  : Installs the database used by WSUS into WID.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : WSUS Services
Description  : Installs the services used by Windows Server 
               Update Services: Update Service, the Reporting 
               Web Service, the API Remoting Web Service, the 
               Client Web Service, the Simple Web Authentication 
               Web Service, the Server Synchronization Service, 
               and the DSS Authentication Web Service.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : SQL Server Connectivity
Description  : Installs the feature that enables WSUS to connect 
               to a Microsoft SQL Server database.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : .NET Framework 3.5 Features
Description  : .NET Framework 3.5 combines the power of the .NET 
               Framework 2.0 APIs with new technologies for 
               building applications that offer appealing user 
               interfaces, protect your customers' personal 
               identity information, enable seamless and secure 
               communication, and provide the ability to model a 
               range of business processes.
Installed    : True
InstallState : Installed

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : .NET Framework 3.5 (includes .NET 2.0 and 3.0)
Description  : .NET Framework 3.5 combines the power of the .NET 
               Framework 2.0 APIs with new technologies for 
               building applications that offer appealing user 
               interfaces, protect your customers' personal 
               identity information, enable seamless and secure 
               communication, and provide the ability to model a 
               range of business processes.
Installed    : True
InstallState : Installed

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : HTTP Activation
Description  : HTTP Activation supports process activation via 
               HTTP. Applications that use HTTP Activation can 
               start and stop dynamically in response to work 
               items that arrive over the network via HTTP.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Non-HTTP Activation
Description  : Non-HTTP Activation supports process activation 
               via Message Queuing, TCP and named pipes. 
               Applications that use Non-HTTP Activation can 
               start and stop dynamically in response to work 
               items that arrive over the network via Message 
               Queuing, TCP and named pipes.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : .NET Framework 4.6 Features
Description  : .NET Framework 4.6 provides a comprehensive and 
               consistent programming model for quickly and 
               easily building and running applications that are 
               built for various platforms including desktop 
               PCs, Servers, smart phones and the public and 
               private cloud.
Installed    : True
InstallState : Installed

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : .NET Framework 4.6
Description  : .NET Framework 4.6 provides a comprehensive and 
               consistent programming model for quickly and 
               easily building and running applications that are 
               built for various platforms including desktop 
               PCs, Servers, smart phones and the public and 
               private cloud.
Installed    : True
InstallState : Installed

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : ASP.NET 4.6
Description  : ASP.NET 4.6 provides core support for running 
               ASP.NET 4.6 stand-alone applications as well as 
               applications that are integrated with IIS.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : WCF Services
Description  : Windows Communication Foundation (WCF) Activation 
               uses Windows Process Activation Service to invoke 
               applications remotely over the network by using 
               protocols such as HTTP, Message Queuing, TCP, and 
               named pipes. Consequently, applications can start 
               and stop dynamically in response to incoming work 
               items, resulting in application hosting that is 
               more robust, manageable, and efficient.
Installed    : True
InstallState : Installed

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : HTTP Activation
Description  : HTTP Activation supports process activation via 
               HTTP. Applications that use HTTP Activation can 
               start and stop dynamically in response to work 
               items that arrive over the network via HTTP.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Message Queuing (MSMQ) Activation
Description  : Message Queuing Activation supports process 
               activation via Message Queuing. Applications that 
               use Message Queuing Activation can start and stop 
               dynamically in response to work items that arrive 
               over the network via Message Queuing.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Named Pipe Activation
Description  : Named Pipes Activation supports process 
               activation via named pipes. Applications that use 
               Named Pipes Activation can start and stop 
               dynamically in response to work items that arrive 
               over the network via named pipes.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : TCP Activation
Description  : TCP Activation supports process activation via 
               TCP. Applications that use TCP Activation can 
               start and stop dynamically in response to work 
               items that arrive over the network via TCP.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : TCP Port Sharing
Description  : TCP Port Sharing allows multiple net.tcp 
               applications to share a single TCP port. 
               Consequently, these applications can coexist on 
               the same physical computer in separate, isolated 
               processes, while sharing the network 
               infrastructure required to send and receive 
               traffic over a TCP port, such as port 808.
Installed    : True
InstallState : Installed

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Background Intelligent Transfer Service (BITS)
Description  : Background Intelligent Transfer Service (BITS) 
               asynchronously transfers files in the foreground 
               or background, controls the flow of the transfers 
               to preserve the responsiveness of other network 
               applications, and automatically resumes file 
               transfers after disconnecting from the network or 
               restarting the computer.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Compact Server
Description  : BITS Compact Server is a stand-alone HTTPS file 
               server that lets you transfer a limited number of 
               large files asynchronously between computers in 
               the same domain or mutually-trusted domains.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : BitLocker Drive Encryption
Description  : BitLocker Drive Encryption helps to protect data 
               on lost, stolen, or inappropriately 
               decommissioned computers by encrypting the entire 
               volume and checking the integrity of early boot 
               components. Data is only decrypted if those 
               components are successfully verified and the 
               encrypted drive is located in the original 
               computer. Integrity checking requires a 
               compatible Trusted Platform Module (TPM).
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : BranchCache
Description  : <a href="http://go.microsoft.com/fwlink/?LinkId=24
               4672">BranchCache</a> installs the services 
               required to configure this computer as either a 
               hosted cache server or a BranchCache-enabled 
               content server. If you are deploying a content 
               server, it must also be configured as either a 
               Hypertext Transfer Protocol (HTTP) web server or 
               a Background Intelligent Transfer Service 
               (BITS)-based application server. To deploy a 
               BranchCache-enabled file server, use the Add 
               Roles Wizard to install the File Services server 
               role with the File Server and BranchCache for 
               network files role services.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Client for NFS
Description  : Client for NFS enables this computer to access 
               files on UNIX-based NFS servers. When installed, 
               you can configure a computer to connect to UNIX 
               NFS shares that allow anonymous access.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Containers
Description  : Provides services and tools to create and manage 
               Windows Server Containers and their resources.
Installed    : True
InstallState : Installed

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Data Center Bridging
Description  : Data Center Bridging (DCB) is a suite of IEEE 
               standards that are used to enhance Ethernet local 
               area networks by providing hardware-based 
               bandwidth guarantees and transport reliability. 
               Use DCB to help enforce bandwidth allocation on a 
               Converged Network Adapter for offloaded storage 
               traffic such as Internet Small Computer System 
               Interface, RDMA over Converged Ethernet, and 
               Fibre Channel over Ethernet.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Enhanced Storage
Description  : Enhanced Storage enables support for accessing 
               additional functions made available by Enhanced 
               Storage devices. Enhanced Storage devices have 
               built-in safety features that let you control who 
               can access the data on the device.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Failover Clustering
Description  : Failover Clustering allows multiple servers to 
               work together to provide high availability of 
               server roles. Failover Clustering is often used 
               for File Services, virtual machines, database 
               applications, and mail applications.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Group Policy Management
Description  : Group Policy Management is a scriptable Microsoft 
               Management Console (MMC) snap-in, providing a 
               single administrative tool for managing Group 
               Policy across the enterprise. Group Policy 
               Management is the standard tool for managing 
               Group Policy.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : I/O Quality of Service
Description  : Allows configuration of I/O quality-of-service 
               settings such as maximum IO and bandwidth limits 
               on applications.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : IIS Hostable Web Core
Description  : IIS Hostable Web Core enables you to write custom 
               code that will host core IIS functionality in 
               your own application. HWC enables your 
               application to serve HTTP requests and use its 
               own applicationHost.config and root web.config 
               configuration files. The HWC application 
               extension is contained in the hwebcore.dll file.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : IP Address Management (IPAM) Server
Description  : IP Address Management (IPAM) Server provides a 
               central framework for managing your IP address 
               space and corresponding infrastructure servers 
               such as DHCP and DNS. IPAM supports automated 
               discovery of infrastructure servers in an Active 
               Directory forest. IPAM allows you to manage your 
               dynamic and static IPv4 and IPv6 address space, 
               tracks IP address utilization trends, and 
               supports monitoring and management of DNS and 
               DHCP services on your network.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : iSNS Server service
Description  : Internet Storage Name Server (iSNS) provides 
               discovery services for Internet Small Computer 
               System Interface (iSCSI) storage area networks. 
               iSNS processes registration requests, 
               deregistration requests, and queries from iSNS 
               clients.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Management OData IIS Extension
Description  : Management OData IIS Extension is a framework for 
               easily exposing Windows PowerShell cmdlets 
               through an ODATA-based web service running under 
               IIS. After enabling this feature, the user must 
               provide a schema file (which contains definitions 
               of the resources to be exposed) and an 
               implementation of callback interfaces to make the 
               web service functional.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Media Foundation
Description  : Media Foundation, which includes Windows Media 
               Foundation, the Windows Media Format SDK, and a 
               server subset of DirectShow, provides the 
               infrastructure required for applications and 
               services to transcode, analyze, and generate 
               thumbnails for media files. Media Foundation is 
               required by the Desktop Experience.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Message Queuing
Description  : Message Queuing provides guaranteed message 
               delivery, efficient routing, security, and 
               priority-based messaging between applications. 
               Message Queuing also accommodates message 
               delivery between applications that run on 
               different operating systems, use dissimilar 
               network infrastructures, are temporarily offline, 
               or that are running at different times.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Message Queuing Services
Description  : Message Queuing Services provides guaranteed 
               message delivery, efficient routing, security, 
               and priority-based messaging between 
               applications. Message Queuing also accommodates 
               message delivery between applications that run on 
               different operating systems, use dissimilar 
               network infrastructures, are temporarily offline, 
               or that are running at different times.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Message Queuing Server
Description  : Message Queuing Server provides guaranteed 
               message delivery, efficient routing, security, 
               and priority-based messaging. It can be used to 
               implement solutions for both asynchronous and 
               synchronous messaging scenarios.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Directory Service Integration
Description  : Directory Service Integration enables publishing 
               of queue properties to the directory, 
               authentication and encryption of messages using 
               certificates registered in the directory, and 
               routing of messages across directory sites.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : HTTP Support
Description  : HTTP Support enables the sending of messages over 
               HTTP.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Message Queuing Triggers
Description  : Message Queuing Triggers enables the invocation 
               of a COM component or an executable depending on 
               the filters that you define for the incoming 
               messages in a given queue.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Routing Service
Description  : Routing Service routes messages between different 
               sites and within a site.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Message Queuing DCOM Proxy
Description  : Message Queuing DCOM Proxy enables this computer 
               to act as a DCOM client of a remote Message 
               Queuing server.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Multipath I/O
Description  : Multipath I/O, along with the Microsoft Device 
               Specific Module (DSM) or a third-party DSM, 
               provides support for using multiple data paths to 
               a storage device on Windows.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : MultiPoint Connector
Description  : Allows your computer to be monitored and managed 
               by the MultiPoint Manager and MultiPoint 
               Dashboard apps.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : MultiPoint Connector Services
Description  : Allows your computer to be monitored and managed 
               by the MultiPoint Manager and MultiPoint 
               Dashboard apps.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : MultiPoint Manager and MultiPoint Dashboard
Description  : GUI tools for managing MultiPoint.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Network Load Balancing
Description  : Network Load Balancing (NLB) distributes traffic 
               across several servers, using the TCP/IP 
               networking protocol. NLB is particularly useful 
               for ensuring that stateless applications, such as 
               Web servers running Internet Information Services 
               (IIS), are scalable by adding additional servers 
               as the load increases.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Peer Name Resolution Protocol
Description  : Peer Name Resolution Protocol allows applications 
               to register and resolve names on your computer so 
               that other computers can communicate with these 
               applications.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Quality Windows Audio Video Experience
Description  : Quality Windows Audio Video Experience (qWave) is 
               a networking platform for audio video (AV) 
               streaming applications on IP home networks. qWave 
               enhances AV streaming performance and reliability 
               by ensuring network quality-of-service (QoS) for 
               AV applications. It provides mechanisms for 
               admission control, run time monitoring and 
               enforcement, application feedback, and traffic 
               prioritization. On Windows Server platforms, 
               qWave provides only rate-of-flow and 
               prioritization services.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Remote Differential Compression
Description  : Remote Differential Compression computes and 
               transfers the differences between two objects 
               over a network using minimal bandwidth.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Remote Server Administration Tools
Description  : Remote Server Administration Tools includes 
               snap-ins and command-line tools for remotely 
               managing roles and features.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Feature Administration Tools
Description  : Feature Administration Tools includes snap-ins 
               and command-line tools for remotely managing 
               features.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : BitLocker Drive Encryption Administration 
               Utilities
Description  : BitLocker Drive Encryption Administration 
               Utilities include snap-ins and command-line tools 
               for managing BitLocker Drive Encryption features.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : DataCenterBridging LLDP Tools
Description  : DataCenterBridging LLDP Tools includes Powershell 
               tools for managing LLDP Agents on the Server
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Failover Clustering Tools
Description  : Failover Clustering Tools include the Failover 
               Cluster Manager snap-in, the Cluster-Aware 
               Updating interface, and the Failover Cluster 
               module for Windows PowerShell. Additional tools 
               are the Failover Cluster Automation Server and 
               the Failover Cluster Command Interface.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Failover Cluster Module for Windows PowerShell
Description  : The Failover Cluster Module for Windows 
               PowerShell includes Windows PowerShell cmdlets 
               for managing failover clusters.  It also includes 
               the Cluster-Aware Updating module for Windows 
               PowerShell, for installing software updates on 
               failover clusters.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Failover Cluster Automation Server
Description  : Failover Cluster Automation Server is the 
               deprecated Component Object Model (COM) 
               programmatic interface, MSClus.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Failover Cluster Command Interface
Description  : Failover Cluster Command Interface is the 
               deprecated cluster.exe command-line tool for 
               Failover Clustering. This tool has been replaced 
               by the Failover Clustering module for Windows 
               PowerShell.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : IP Address Management (IPAM) Client
Description  : IP Address Management (IPAM) Client is used to 
               connect to and manage a local or remote IPAM 
               server. IPAM provides a central framework for 
               managing IP address space and corresponding 
               infrastructure servers such as DHCP and DNS in an 
               Active Directory forest.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Shielded VM Tools
Description  : Shielded VM Tools includes the Provisioning Data 
               File Wizard and the Template Disk Wizard.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Storage Replica Module for Windows PowerShell
Description  : Storage Replica Module for Windows PowerShell 
               includes the CIM provider and the Storage Replica 
               module for Windows PowerShell.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Role Administration Tools
Description  : Role Administration Tools includes snap-ins and 
               command-line tools for remotely managing roles.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : AD DS and AD LDS Tools
Description  : Active Directory Domain Services (AD DS) and 
               Active Directory Lightweight Directory Services 
               (AD LDS) Tools includes snap-ins and command-line 
               tools for remotely managing AD DS and AD LDS.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Active Directory module for Windows PowerShell
Description  : The Active Directory module for Windows PowerShel 
               and the tools it provides can be used by Active 
               Directory administrators to manage Active 
               Directory Domain Services (AD DS) at the command 
               line.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : AD DS Tools
Description  : Active Directory Domain Services (AD DS) Tools 
               includes snap-ins and command-line tools for 
               remotely managing AD DS.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Active Directory Administrative Center
Description  : Active Directory Administrative Center provides 
               users and network administrators with an enhanced 
               Active Directory data management experience and a 
               rich graphical user interface (GUI) to perform 
               common Active Directory object management tasks.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : AD DS Snap-Ins and Command-Line Tools
Description  : Active Directory Domain Services Snap-Ins and 
               Command-Line Tools includes Active Directory 
               Users and Computers, Active Directory Domains and 
               Trusts, Active Directory Sites and Services, and 
               other snap-ins and command-line tools for 
               remotely managing Active Directory domain 
               controllers.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : AD LDS Snap-Ins and Command-Line Tools
Description  : Active Directory Lightweight Directory Services 
               (AD LDS) Snap-Ins and Command-Line Tools includes 
               Active Directory Sites and Services, ADSI Edit, 
               Schema Manager, and other snap-ins and 
               command-line tools for managing AD LDS.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Hyper-V Management Tools
Description  : Hyper-V Management Tools includes GUI and 
               command-line tools for managing Hyper-V.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Hyper-V Module for Windows PowerShell
Description  : Hyper-V Module for Windows PowerShell includes 
               Windows PowerShell cmdlets for managing Hyper-V.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Windows Server Update Services Tools
Description  : Windows Server Update Services Tools includes 
               graphical and Powershell tools for managing WSUS.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : API and PowerShell cmdlets
Description  : Installs the .NET API and PowerShell cmdlets for 
               remote management, automated task creation, and 
               managing WSUS from the command line.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : DHCP Server Tools
Description  : DHCP Server Tools includes the DHCP MMC snap-in, 
               DHCP server netsh context and Windows PowerShell 
               module for DHCP Server.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : DNS Server Tools
Description  : DNS Server Tools includes the DNS Manager 
               snap-in, dnscmd.exe command-line tool and Windows 
               PowerShell module for DNS Server.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Remote Access Management Tools
Description  : Remote Access Management Tools includes graphical 
               and PowerShell tools for managing Remote Access.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Remote Access module for Windows PowerShell
Description  : Includes the Remote Access provider and cmdlets. 
               Remote Access administrators can use the Windows 
               PowerShell environment and the tools it provides 
               to manage Remote Access at the command line.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : RPC over HTTP Proxy
Description  : Remote Procedure Call (RPC) over HTTP Proxy 
               relays RPC traffic from client applications over 
               HTTP to the server as an alternative to clients 
               accessing the server over a VPN connection.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Setup and Boot Event Collection
Description  : This feature enables the collection and logging 
               of setup and boot events from other computers on 
               this network.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Simple TCP/IP Services
Description  : Simple TCP/IP Services supports the following 
               TCP/IP services: Character Generator, Daytime, 
               Discard, Echo and Quote of the Day. Simple TCP/IP 
               Services is provided for backward compatibility 
               and should not be installed unless it is required.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : SMB 1.0/CIFS File Sharing Support
Description  : Support for the SMB 1.0/CIFS file sharing 
               protocol, and the Computer Browser protocol.
Installed    : True
InstallState : Installed

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : SMB Bandwidth Limit
Description  : SMB Bandwidth Limit provides a mechanism to track 
               SMB traffic per category (Default, Hyper-V or 
               Live Migration) and allows you to limit the 
               amount of traffic allowed for a given category. 
               It is commonly used to limit the bandwidth used 
               by Live Migration over SMB.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : SNMP Service
Description  : Simple Network Management Protocol (SNMP) Service 
               includes agents that monitor the activity in 
               network devices and report to the network console 
               workstation.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : SNMP WMI Provider
Description  : SNMP Windows Management Instrumentation (WMI) 
               Provider enables WMI client scripts and 
               applications to access SNMP information. Clients 
               can use WMI C++ interfaces and scripting objects 
               to communicate with network devices that use the 
               SNMP protocol and can receive SNMP traps as WMI 
               events.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Telnet Client
Description  : Telnet Client uses the Telnet protocol to connect 
               to a remote Telnet server and run applications on 
               that server.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : VM Shielding Tools for Fabric Management
Description  : Provides Shielded VM utilities that are used by 
               Fabric Management solutions and should be 
               installed on the Fabric Management server.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Windows Defender Features
Description  : Windows Defender helps protect your machine from 
               malware.
Installed    : True
InstallState : Installed

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Windows Defender
Description  : Windows Defender helps protect your machine from 
               malware.
Installed    : True
InstallState : Installed

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Windows Internal Database
Description  : Windows Internal Database is a relational data 
               store that can be used only by Windows roles and 
               features, such as Active Directory Rights 
               Management Services, Windows Server Update 
               Services, and Windows System Resource Manager.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Windows PowerShell
Description  : Windows PowerShell enables you to automate local 
               and remote Windows administration. This 
               task-based command-line shell and scripting 
               language is built on the Microsoft .NET 
               Framework. It includes hundreds of built-in 
               commands and lets you write and distribute your 
               own commands and scripts.
Installed    : True
InstallState : Installed

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Windows PowerShell 5.1
Description  : Windows PowerShell enables you to automate local 
               and remote Windows administration. This 
               task-based command-line shell and scripting 
               language is built on the Microsoft .NET 
               Framework. It includes hundreds of built-in 
               commands and lets you write and distribute your 
               own commands and scripts.
Installed    : True
InstallState : Installed

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Windows PowerShell 2.0 Engine
Description  : Windows PowerShell 2.0 Engine includes the core 
               components from Windows PowerShell 2.0 for 
               backward compatibility with existing Windows 
               PowerShell host applications.
Installed    : True
InstallState : Installed

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Windows PowerShell Desired State Configuration 
               Service
Description  : Windows PowerShell Desired State Configuration 
               Service supports configuration management of 
               multiple nodes from a single repository.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Windows PowerShell Web Access
Description  : Windows PowerShell Web Access lets a server act 
               as a web gateway, through which an organization's 
               users can manage remote computers by running 
               Windows PowerShell sessions in a web browser. 
               After Windows PowerShell Web Access is installed, 
               an administrator completes the gateway 
               configuration in the Web Server (IIS) management 
               console.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Windows Process Activation Service
Description  : Windows Process Activation Service generalizes 
               the IIS process model, removing the dependency on 
               HTTP. All the features of IIS that were 
               previously available only to HTTP applications 
               are now available to applications hosting Windows 
               Communication Foundation (WCF) services, using 
               non-HTTP protocols. IIS 10.0 also uses Windows 
               Process Activation Service for message-based 
               activation over HTTP.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Process Model
Description  : Process Model hosts Web and WCF services. 
               Introduced with IIS 6.0, the process model is a 
               new architecture that features rapid failure 
               protection, health monitoring, and recycling. 
               Windows Process Activation Service Process Model 
               removes the dependency on HTTP.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : .NET Environment 3.5
Description  : .NET Environment supports managed code activation 
               in the process model.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Configuration APIs
Description  : Configuration APIs enable applications that are 
               built using the .NET Framework to configure 
               Windows Process Activation Model 
               programmatically. This lets the application 
               developer automatically configure Windows Process 
               Activation Model settings when the application 
               runs instead of requiring the administrator to 
               manually configure these settings.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Windows Server Backup
Description  : Windows Server Backup allows you to back up and 
               recover your operating system, applications and 
               data. You can schedule backups, and protect the 
               entire server or specific volumes.
Installed    : True
InstallState : Installed

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Windows Server Migration Tools
Description  : Windows Server Migration Tools includes Windows 
               PowerShell cmdlets that facilitate migration of 
               server roles, operating system settings, files, 
               and shares from computers that are running 
               earlier versions of Windows Server or Windows 
               Server 2012 to computers that are running Windows 
               Server 2012.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : Windows Standards-Based Storage Management
Description  : Windows Standards-Based Storage Management 
               provides the ability to discover, manage, and 
               monitor storage devices using management 
               interfaces that conform to the SMI-S standard. 
               This functionality is exposed as a set of Windows 
               Management Instrumentation (WMI) classes and 
               Windows PowerShell cmdlets.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : WinRM IIS Extension
Description  : Windows Remote Management (WinRM) IIS Extension 
               enables a server to receive a management request 
               from a client by using WS-Management. WinRM is 
               the Microsoft implementation of the WS-Management 
               protocol which provides a secure way to 
               communicate with local and remote computers by 
               using Web services.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : WINS Server
Description  : Windows Internet Naming Service (WINS) Server 
               provides a distributed database for registering 
               and querying dynamic mappings of NetBIOS names 
               for computers and groups used on your network. 
               WINS maps NetBIOS names to IP addresses and 
               solves the problems arising from NetBIOS name 
               resolution in routed environments.
Installed    : False
InstallState : Available

Report       : 6/4/2021 11:33 AM
DisplayName  : WoW64 Support
Description  : Includes all of WoW64 to support running 32-bit 
               applications on Server Core installations.  This 
               feature is required for full Server 
               installations. Uninstalling WoW64 Support will 
               convert a full Server installation into a Server 
               Core installation.
Installed    : True
InstallState : Installed



