                         Windows Server Feature Report [6/4/2021 11:33 AM]

********
* SRV1 *
********
    .NET Framework 3.5 (includes .NET 2.0 and 3.0)
    ______________________________________________
    .NET Framework 3.5 combines the power of the .NET Framework 2.0 APIs with new technologies for building applications that offer appealing user interfaces, protect your customers' personal identity information, enable seamless and secure communication, and provide the ability to model a range of business processes.

    .NET Framework 3.5 Features
    ___________________________
    .NET Framework 3.5 combines the power of the .NET Framework 2.0 APIs with new technologies for building applications that offer appealing user interfaces, protect your customers' personal identity information, enable seamless and secure communication, and provide the ability to model a range of business processes.

    .NET Framework 4.6
    __________________
    .NET Framework 4.6 provides a comprehensive and consistent programming model for quickly and easily building and running applications that are built for various platforms including desktop PCs, Servers, smart phones and the public and private cloud.

    .NET Framework 4.6 Features
    ___________________________
    .NET Framework 4.6 provides a comprehensive and consistent programming model for quickly and easily building and running applications that are built for various platforms including desktop PCs, Servers, smart phones and the public and private cloud.

    Containers
    __________
    Provides services and tools to create and manage Windows Server Containers and their resources.

    File and iSCSI Services
    _______________________
    File and iSCSI Services provides technologies that help you manage file servers and storage, reduce disk space utilization, replicate and cache files to branch offices, move or fail over a file share to another cluster node, and share files by using the NFS protocol.

    File and Storage Services
    _________________________
    File and Storage Services includes services that are always installed, as well as functionality that you can install to help manage file servers and storage.

    File Server
    ___________
    File Server manages shared folders and enables users to access files on this computer from the network.

    SMB 1.0/CIFS File Sharing Support
    _________________________________
    Support for the SMB 1.0/CIFS file sharing protocol, and the Computer Browser protocol.

    Storage Services
    ________________
    Storage Services provides storage management functionality that is always installed and cannot be removed.

    TCP Port Sharing
    ________________
    TCP Port Sharing allows multiple net.tcp applications to share a single TCP port. Consequently, these applications can coexist on the same physical computer in separate, isolated processes, while sharing the network infrastructure required to send and receive traffic over a TCP port, such as port 808.

    WCF Services
    ____________
    Windows Communication Foundation (WCF) Activation uses Windows Process Activation Service to invoke applications remotely over the network by using protocols such as HTTP, Message Queuing, TCP, and named pipes. Consequently, applications can start and stop dynamically in response to incoming work items, resulting in application hosting that is more robust, manageable, and efficient.

    Windows Defender
    ________________
    Windows Defender helps protect your machine from malware.

    Windows Defender Features
    _________________________
    Windows Defender helps protect your machine from malware.

    Windows PowerShell
    __________________
    Windows PowerShell enables you to automate local and remote Windows administration. This task-based command-line shell and scripting language is built on the Microsoft .NET Framework. It includes hundreds of built-in commands and lets you write and distribute your own commands and scripts.

    Windows PowerShell 2.0 Engine
    _____________________________
    Windows PowerShell 2.0 Engine includes the core components from Windows PowerShell 2.0 for backward compatibility with existing Windows PowerShell host applications.

    Windows PowerShell 5.1
    ______________________
    Windows PowerShell enables you to automate local and remote Windows administration. This task-based command-line shell and scripting language is built on the Microsoft .NET Framework. It includes hundreds of built-in commands and lets you write and distribute your own commands and scripts.

    Windows Server Backup
    _____________________
    Windows Server Backup allows you to back up and recover your operating system, applications and data. You can schedule backups, and protect the entire server or specific volumes.

    WoW64 Support
    _____________
    Includes all of WoW64 to support running 32-bit applications on Server Core installations.  This feature is required for full Server installations. Uninstalling WoW64 Support will convert a full Server installation into a Server Core installation.

